Guide to the Art Poster File ca. 1890-1910 PR55-1
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Newspaper Posters, 3
  - The Sun World/ Aug. 16/ Say! Im der Yellow Kid of Hogan's Alley (Outcault, R. F.), 1896/08/16 (Item PR-055-001-0591)
  - The Sunday World/ Max Nordau's Startling Views on Americans/ Strange Claw-Figured People in New York (Gihon, A. D.), 1896/08/23 (Item PR-055-001-0592)
  - The Sunday World/ McDougall Shows New York to Li Hung Chang (Haskell, Ernest (1876-1925)), 1896/08/30 (Item PR-055-001-0593)
  - The Sunday World/ A Strange Combination of Love, Poverty, Millions and Law, 1896/09/06 (Item PR-055-001-0594)
  - The Christmas World/ Out Sunday Dec. 13th/ Christmas with the Poor and Christmas with the Rich, 1896/12/13 (Item PR-055-001-0595)
  - The New York Tribune, Poster No. 1/ The Golden Era of Protection, 1888-92, 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0596)
  - The New York Tribune, Poster No. 2/ 1893 to '96/ The True Storm of Tens of Thousands of Homes in America after the McKinley Bill had been Repealed, 1896/00/00? (Item PR-055-001-0597)
  - The New York Tribune/ Poster No. 3/ Populist Bunco Game of 1896: Bryan's Panacea is Purest Moonshine: "Open the Mints to the Silver of the World", 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0598)
  - The New York Tribune, Poster No. 4/ The Key to the Situation, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0599)
  - Philadelphia Sunday Press (Brill, George Reiter?), 1895/10/13 (Item PR-055-001-0600)
  - Philadelphia Sunday Press (Brill, George Reiter?), 1895/10/20 (Item PR-055-001-0601)
  - Philadelphia Sunday Press/ "My Easter Hat"/ Free to Every Reader (Brill, George Reiter?), 1896/04/05 (Item PR-055-001-0602)
  - Philadelphia Sunday Press/ Wonderful Base Ball/ Novelty Free to Every Reader (Brill, George Reiter?), 1896/05/03? (Item PR-055-001-0603)
  - Philadelphia Sunday Press/ Exact Reproduction of the Great Battleship New York Free (Brill, George Reiter), 1896/03/10 (Item PR-055-001-0604)
  - Philadelphia Sunday Press/ All Hay Ride/ A Complete Trolley Car/ Free to Every Reader (Brill, George Reiter?), 1896/07/21 (Item PR-055-001-0605)
  - The Boston Sunday Herald/ Another Attractive Colored Supplement, 1895/03/03 (Item PR-055-001-0606)
  - The Boston Sunday Herald, 1896/04/26 (Item PR-055-001-0607)
  - The Boston Sunday Herald/ Issues Each Week A/ Pretty and Up-To-Date/ Colored Supplement, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0608)
  - Chicago Sunday Tribune/ Veterans of the War (Brill, George Reiter), 1895/05/26 (Item PR-055-001-0609)
  - Chicago Tribune/ Chicago's Big Elevators (Brill, George Reiter?), 1895/07/14 (Item PR-055-001-0610)
  - Chicago Sunday Tribune/ Several Pages of Bicycle Fact, Fun, Poetry and Fiction (Brill, George Reiter?), 1895/00/00 or 1896/00/00? (Item PR-055-001-0611)
  - The New York Herald Sunday/ Easter Number/ Music/ Poems/ Sermons (Rhead, Louis John (1857-1926)), 1896/03/22 (Item PR-055-001-0612)
  - New York Ledger/ $1000 in Cash Prizes (Eddy, Henry Brevoort), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0613)
  - New York Ledger (Eddy, Henry Brevoort), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0614)
  - The New York Ledger/ Maubikeck, The Lion-Tamer/ by Seward W. Hopkins/ See Other Side (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0615)
  - "The Queen of Finesse"/ In the New York Ledger (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0616)
  - The New York Recorder/ contains all the news of the Great Cycle Show at Madison Square Garden (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0617)
  - The Evening Telegram/ Best Cartoons in America (Thorp, J. W.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0618)
  - The Evening Telegram/ Best Cartoons in America (Thorp, J. W.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0619)
  - Vanity/ The New Weekly Paper, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0620)
  - Vanity/ Price 10 cents/ For Sale Here, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0621)
  - "Young Sports"/ American Boys Read the Best Boys Paper, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0622)